

## **PROFILE**

Developer at CloudRaker, specialty in javascript frameworks. Primarily frontend, some backend experience.

Freelance musician, teaching and playing the electric bass across genres. Born and raised in Seattle.

Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng) in Materials Engineering from McGill University.

See portfolio (<u>hymowitz.org</u>) for currently maintained personal projects in coding, music, and photography

### CONTACT

- **(**438) 825 9185
- hymowitz.org
- ehymowitz

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

CLOUDRAKER | NOVEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

- Primary tech: React / React frameworks + Typescript, Angular, MongoDB, NestJS
- Regularly consults non-technical team members to plan technical aspects of projects
- Involved in building and maintaining simultaneous websites and web-apps for different clients

#### LE WAGON WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP, TA

JUNE 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

- g-week intensive course covering Ruby, OOP, HTML, SCSS, UI/UX, JS, SQL, and Rails
- Provided guidance to students on how to approach code challenges
- Assisted multiple student teams in the creation and completion of full stack web projects

# CONTENT COORDINATOR / BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT COORDINATOR

HAPLY ROBOTICS | JAN 2018 - DEC 2019

- Web/media content designer and creator
- Business development explorer and liaison between technical team and clients
- Development of technical demos for teaching and capturing user feedback

### **EDUCATION**

#### MCGILL UNIVERSITY

B.ENG MATERIALS ENGINEERING (CO-OP PROGRAM) CLASS OF 2017

- Department Leadership: VP External, Year Representative
- Founding President of 3D Printing Design Team
- Internships in Aerospace (Pratt & Whitney Canada), and Composite Materials Lab

### MUSIC

#### COMMUNITY

- Self taught through online resources and passion for music
- Active in the Montreal scene in both jam sessions and organized shows
- Bandleading and events organizing experience

#### **BASS GUITAR**

- Teacher of performance technique and theory
- Performed at Montreal venues including MTELUS and Nomad Live (ArtJam) as a session/gig musician
- Recording musician See portfolio for Spotify links
- Genres include but not limited to country, soul, funk, hip-hop, jazz